const data = [
    {
        question: "If we want define style for an unique element, then which css selector will we use ?",
        options: ["Id","text","name","class"],
        correct_option: "Id"
    },
    {
        question: "If we don't want to allow a floating div to the left side of an element, which css property will we use ?",
        options: ["margin","clear","padding"],
        correct_option: "clear"
    },
    {
        question: "Suppose we want to arrange five nos. of DIVs so that DIV4 is placed above DIV1. Now, which css property will we use to control the order of stack?",
        options: ["d-index","y-index","x-index","z-index"],
        correct_option: "z-index"
    },
    {
        question: "Can we align a Block element by setting the left and right margins ?",
        options: ["Yes, we can", "Not Possible"],
        correct_option: "Not Possible"
    },
    {
        question: "If we want to wrap a block of text around an image, which css property will we use ?",
        options: ["push","align","float","wrap"],
        correct_option: "float"
    },
    {
        question: "If we want to show an Arrow as cursor, then which value we will use ?",
        options: ["default","arr","pointer","arrow"],
        correct_option: "default"
    },
    {
        question: "If we want to use a nice looking green dotted border around an image, which css property will we use?",
        options: ["border-line","border-style","border-color","border-decoration"],
        correct_option: "border-style"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following properties will we use to display border around a cell without any content ?",
        options: ["void-cell","noncoherent-cell","empty-cell","blank-cell"],
        correct_option: "empty-cell"
    },
    {
        question: "What should be the table width, so that the width of a table adjust to the current width of the browser window?",
        options: ["640 pixels","full-screen","1024 px","100%"],
        correct_option: "100%"
    },
    {
        question: "Which element is used in the <HEAD> section on an HTML / XHTMLpage, if we want to use an external style sheet file to decorate the page ?",
        options: ["<src>","<css>","<link>","<style>"],
        correct_option: "<link>"
    },
];

export default data